<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[LADY KIWI]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[LADY KIWI]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/ladykiwi/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 04:10:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/ladykiwi/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CLICK HERE FOR ROSES EP]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>CLICK HERE FOR ROSES EP</h1><p></p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ladykiwi/roses-ep/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b9f5f443-130c-4809-9d2a-658aa3d78eb8</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 04:10:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BIO]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>BIO</h1><p>Oluwakemi Gabriela Reyes Akinbileje, who also goes by Lady Kiwi, is a creative experimental artist and entrepreneur of Honduran and Nigerian descent. Born and raised in the DC metropolitan area, she is ringing in a new era with her diverse talents that bring timely messages to the tune of pop, rap, alternative, and other genres. Lady Kiwi jump-started her performing career at the age of 4 years old when she landed a leading role at a performing arts summer camp, and self-recorded her first song when she was 11 years old. She started taking music seriously in 2008 when she began collaborations with other artists residing in the DC Metropolitan area. She is a 2013 graduate from the International Baccalaureate program at South Lakes High School in Reston, Virginia. Kemi's girl scouting days have taken her from the Daisies to the Ambassadors level, reflecting nearly one dozen years of sisterhood and growth with her Girl Scout sisters. She has earned much recognition including, the Leadership Torch, Silver Trefoil Award, and Silver Award. As a Gold Award recipient, Kemi developed the "Young Artists' Creative Table," where she lead young artists to connect with accomplished music professionals. Participants delved into the world of music, entrepreneurship, intellectual property, and copyright law. In the fall of 2013, Kemi began her studies at the Clive Davis Institute of Recorded Music within the Tisch School of the Arts at New York University, where she studied music business and entrepreneurship. After completing classes relevant to branding and marketing, her years of service has led her to found LOUD Kingdom, a non-profit strategic charity and community service organization, in order to reach out to those in need. She hopes to inspire her clients through her love and passion for branding, music, and artistry. She is a songwriter, producer, singer, rapper, guitarist, pianist, violinist, dancer, choreographer, and emerging executive. Keep your eyes fixed on the horizon for Kemi, rising performer and entrepreneur--like no one has ever seen before.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ladykiwi/bio/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0cba9687-b0e2-4b9b-83fd-4f0be55ef79a</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 16:40:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RESUME]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>RESUME</h1><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/vahj1ThiexotieMo/b5bd5b018e9607cd3c93f5a3a057b2b6/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=1056&cropwidth=815&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2F00ad97b4-18ad-459c-86fe-7b1e7f0db5d9.jpg&x=0&y=0"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ladykiwi/resume/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0d6fa382-bb55-4f5e-9525-e949e05b36d1</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2016 10:08:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Join Lady Kiwi as she talks about Beyonce, Recording Techniques, Time Management, and much more.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Join Lady Kiwi as she talks about Beyonce, Recording Techniques, Time Management, and much more.</h1><p>VIDEO: INSPIRATION</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/81b93dbf-0410-44a9-bdbe-8e485b90e1c1.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ladykiwi/join-lady-kiwi-as-she-talks-beyonce-recording-techniques-t/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1d7e1cc1-02fb-4372-9b75-7cfe57f0182c</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2016 09:40:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>